A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2013.101: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2013; AC_2013_101; 23.58 Cubic Feet 18 standard record storage boxes, R4224-R4241; 18 standard record storage boxes, R4224-R4241
  - Innovation Equity Project (IEP), AC_2013_101_3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2006 IEP 001 - (INNOVATION EQUITY PROJECT) - STRATEGIC PLANNING (Box R4238)
    - 2006 IEP 002 - (INNOVATION EQUITY PROJECT) - CLIMATE CHANGE STRATEGIC PLANNING, 2006-2007 (Box R4238)
  - Innovation (INN), AC_2013_101_4; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2007 INN 001 - (INNOVATION) - SOCIAL ENTREPRENEUR DINNERS (Box R4238)
    - 2007 INN 201 - RURAL INNOVATIONS NETWORK (INDIA) - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP, 2007-2009 (Box R4238)
    - 2007 INN 202 - GLOBAL ALLIANCE FOR TB DRUG DEVELOPMENT - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP, 2007-2009 (Box R4238)
    - 2007 INN 205 - RURAL INNOVATIONS NETWORK (INDIA) - TECHNOLOGICAL INNOVATIONS IN RURAL INDIA, 2007-2012 (Box R4238)
    - 2007 INN 208 - SUNNIGHT SOLAR - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP, 2007-2010 (Box R4238)
    - 2007 INN 209 - AMAZON CONSERVATION ASSOCIATION - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP (RESCINDED), 2007-2008 (Box R4238)
    - 2007 INN 210 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (ENGLAND) - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP, 2007-2009 (Box R4238)
    - 2008 INN 301 - IDEO, INC - INNOVATION DESIGN SCALING PROGRAM, 2007-2009 (Box R4238)
    - 2008 INN 303 - INTERNATIONAL AIDS VACCINE INITIATIVE - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP, 2008-2009 (Box R4238)
    - 2008 INN 304 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT DESIGN SUMMIT, 2008-2009 (Box R4238)
    - 2008 INN 305 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP - PHILANTHROPIC INNOVATION SUPPORT SYSTEM (Box R4238)
    - 2008 INN 306 - TUFTS UNIVERSITY - POSITIVE DEVIANCE INITIATIVE, 2007-2013 (Box R4238)
    - 2008 INN 306 - Positive Deviance Initiative-Digital Material, 2007-2013; 2013:101:024 (Item 2013:101:024)
    - 2008 INN 306 - Prakarsa Inovatif - Digital Material, 2007-2013; 2013:101:025 (Item 2013:101:025)
    - 2008 INN 307 - DESIGN CONTINUUM ? BC CONFERENCE: DESIGN FOR SOCIAL IMPACT, 2008-2009 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INN 308 - VISIONSPRING - EYE CARE NEEDS FOR POOR, 2008-2011 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INN 310 - WINTERHOUSE - DESIGN FOR SOCIAL IMPACT AND INNOVATION, 2008-2012 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INN 311 - ZAGO LLC - HUMAN-CENTERED DESIGN INNOVATION, 2008-2012 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INN 312 - GLOBALGIVING FOUNDATION - INNOCENTIVE PARTNERSHIP, 2007-2009 (Box R4239)
  - American Workers Income (AWI), AC_2013_101_5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 AWI 301 - GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY - RETIREMENT SECURITY PROJECT, 2008-2010 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 AWI 302 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SOCIAL INSURANCE - INNOVATION GRANTS TO STRENGTHEN SOCIAL SECURITY, 2008-2009 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 AWI 303 - TOWERS PERRIN - ANALYSES FOR DEVELOPMENT OF PRODUCTS AND POLICIES FOR THE ECONOMIC SECURITY OF LOW- AND MODERATE-INCOME AMERICAN WORKERS, 2008-2009 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 AWI 304 - EDUCATION AND RESEARCH FUND OF EMPLOYEE BENEFIT RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RETIREMENT CONFIDENCE SURVEY (Box R4239)
    - 2008 AWI 305 - CONSUMER FEDERATION OF AMERICA FOUNDATION - EMERGENCY SAVINGS ISSUES (Box R4239)
    - 2008 AWI 308 - QVISORY - HEALTH CARE AND FINANCIAL PRODUCT ASSESSMENT FOR YOUNG AMERICAN WORKERS, 2008-2011 (Box R4239)
  - INV, AC_2013_101_6; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2008 INV 201 - GLOBAL DEVELOPMENT INCUBATOR - SOCIAL IMPACT INVESTMENT TOOL, 2008-2009 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INV 202 - NONPROFIT FINANCE FUND - SUSTAINABLE ENHANCEMENT GRANT MODEL, 2008-2012 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INV 203 - B LAB - SOCIAL IMPACT INVESTMENT TOOL AND WEB PLATFORM, 2008-2009 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INV 204 - ROOT CAPITAL - PRI TO EXPAND LENDING CAPABILITIES, 2008-2010 (Box R4239)
    - 2008 INV 206 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - ASPEN NETWORK FOR DEVELOPMENT ENTREPRENEURS, 2008-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 207 - CALVERT FOUNDATION - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2008-2010 (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 208 - TECHNOSERVE - AGRIBUSINESS ACCELERATOR, 2008-2010 (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 209 - AGORA PARTNERSHIPS - PROMOTING ENTREPRENEURSHIP IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2008-2012 (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 301 - SOCIAL VENTURE TECHNOLOGY GROUP - RIIC IMPACT METRICS AND STANDARDS PROJECT, 2007-2008 (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 302 - RSF SOCIAL FINANCE - INVESTMENT CAPITAL FOR SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 303 - GLOBAL DEVELOPMENT INCUBATOR - ASPEN NETWORK FOR DEVELOPMENT ENTREPRENEURS, 2008-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2008 INV 305 - ROOT CAPITAL - SUSTAINABLE ENHANCEMENT GRANT METHODOLOGY, 2008-2010 (Box R4240)
  - New Orleans (NOL), AC_2013_101_7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2007 NOL 001 - (NEW ORLEANS) - CONTRACT WITH FELICE L. MICHETTI (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 002 - (NEW ORLEANS) - MEETING, WHAT WORKED?THE RENEWAL OF NEW YORK CITY IN THE 80'S AND 90'S (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 302 - POLICYLINK - EQUITABLE DEVELOPMENT AND LOUISIANA RECOVERY EFFORTS, 2007-2010 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 303 - OFFICE OF RECOVERY MANAGEMENT, CITY OF NEW ORLEANS - RECOVERY ACTIVITIES, 2007-2010 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 304 - OMG CENTER FOR COLLABORATIVE LEARNING - EVALUATION OF REBUILDING NEW ORLEANS INITIATIVE, 2007-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 305 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL: THREE PROJECTS RELATED TO HURRICANE KATRINA, 2007-2011 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 308 - V-DAY - EVENTS TO RAISE AWARENESS ABOUT VIOLENCE AGAINST WOMEN, 2007-2008 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 309 - CHILDREN'S DEFENSE FUND - FREEDOM SCHOOLS PROJECT, 2007-2008 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 310 - NEW ORLEANS REDEVELOPMENT AUTHORITY - COSTS OF KEY STAFF POSITIONS, 2007-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 311 - ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY PARTNERS - AFFORDABLE HOUSING DEVELOPMENT IN NEW ORLEANS, 2007-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 312 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - FORUM FOR SUSTAINED TRANSFORMATION AND RELATED ACTIVITIES, 2007-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 313 - POLICYLINK - CONFERENCE, "REGIONAL EQUITY '08: THIRD NATIONAL SUMMIT", 2007-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 315 - NEW ORLEANS NEIGHBORHOOD DEVELOPMENT COLLABORATIVE - PROPERTY REDEVELOPMENT IN NEW ORLEANS, 2007-2011 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 316 - PROVIDENCE COMMUNITY HOUSING - MIXED INCOME HOUSING PLAN IN NEW ORLEANS, 2007-2008 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 317 - NATIONAL TRUST FOR HISTORIC PRESERVATION - PRESERVATION TRAINING PROGRAM; PRESERVE NOLA NEIGHBORHOODS, 2007-2009 (Box R4240)
    - 2007 NOL 318 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - NEW ORLEANS INDEX, 2007-2010 (Box R4241)
    - 2007 NOL 319 - MUSEUM OF MODERN ART - DIGITALLY FABRICATED HOUSING FOR NEW ORLEANS, 2007-2008 (Box R4241)
    - 2007 NOL319 - Home Delivery: Fabricating the Modern Dwelling - Published Material, 2007-2008; 2013:101:020 (Item 2013:101:020)
    - 2007 NOL 320 - CBNO/MAC FOUNDATION - NEW ORLEANS CITIZEN PARTICIPATION PROGRAM, 2007-2009 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 301 - DANTAS, LUISA - DOCUMENTARY ON THE NEW ORLEANS REBUILDING PROCESS, 2008-2009 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 302 - NEW YORK REGIONAL ASSOCIATION OF GRANTMAKERS - COORDINATE PHILANTHROPIC EFFORTS FOR COMMUNITIES AFFECTED BY HURRICANES KATRINA AND RITA, 2006-2008 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 303 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - RF REDEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 2008-2010 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 304 - GREATER NEW ORLEANS FOUNDATION - COMMUNITY REVITALIZATION PROGRAM, 2007-2012 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 307 - NEW ORLEANS REDEVELOPMENT AUTHORITY - BOLSTER ORGANIZATIONAL CAPACITY, 2008-2010 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 308 - US BIENNIAL, INC. - "PROSPECT.1 NEW ORLEANS" EXHIBITION, 2008-2013 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL308 - Prospect 1 images - Digital Material, 2008-2013; 2013:101:019 (Item 2013:101:019)
    - 2008 NOL 309 - LOCAL INITIATIVES SUPPORT CORPORATION - NATIONAL VACANT PROPERTIES CAMPAIGN, 2007-2011 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 310 - PROVIDENCE COMMUNITY HOUSING - NEWCITY NEIGHBORHOOD PARTNERSHIP, 2008-2010 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 311 - GREATER NEW ORLEANS FOUNDATION - HOUSING RESOURCE CENTER NETWORK; ASSESSMENT OF HOUSING ENTITLEMENT PROGRAM, 2008-2012 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 312 - THE IDEA VILLAGE, INC. - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE FOR PROPOSALS BY RF REDEVELOPMENT FELLOWS, 2008-2011 (Box R4241)
    - 2008 NOL 313 - PATRIZI, PATRICIA - EVALUATION OF NEW ORLEANS INITIATIVE, 2008-2010 (Box R4241)
  - NCG, AC_2013_101_8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 NCG 301 - UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO AT BOULDER - CONSORTIUM FOR CAPACITY BUILDING, 2008-2012 (Box R4240)
- AC.2013.102: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2013; AC_2013_102; 26.2 Cubic Feet 20 standard record storage boxes, R4245-R4264; 20 standard record storage boxes, R4245-R4264
  - Food Security (FS), AC_2013_102_1; 18.34 Cubic Feet 14 record storage boxes
    - 2001 FS 016 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN RICE, 2000-2005 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 017 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; ECONOMICS OF POTATO AND SWEET POTATO PRODUCTION, 2000-2004 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 019 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - MOLECULAR GENETICS OF DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN RICE, 2000-2005 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 029 - (FOOD SECURITY) - ASSESSMENT OF SOIL FERTILITY AND INTEGRATED NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT PROGRAM IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2000-2005 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 032 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - DROUGHT TOLERANT CROPS, 2000-2005 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 037 - SCIENTIFIC and INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT CENTRE (ZIMBABWE) - MAIZE CLONAL PROPAGATION AND SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE, 1999-2005 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 042 - AFRICAN CENTRE FOR FERTILIZER DEVELOPMENT - DISSEMINATION OF SOIL FERTILITY TECHNOLOGIES IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 2000-2005 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 048 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR SUNITA JAIN, 2001-2006 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 055 - MOI UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; ON-FARM SEED PRODUCTION OF MAIZE AND BEANS, 2000-2006 (Box R4245)
    - 2001 FS 057 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; CROP PROTECTION IN SMALLHOLDER SOYBEAN PRODUCTION, 2000-2004 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 065 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - MAIZE GENETIC IMPROVEMENT IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2000-2004 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 076 - WAGENINGEN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (NETHERLANDS) - COLLABORATIVE TRAINING AND RESEARCH PROGRAMME (FIRST COHORT), 2001-2010 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 076 - Stepping-stones to Improve Upon Functioning of Participatory Agricultural Extension Programmes - Published Material, 2001-2010; 2013:102:001 (Item 2013:102:001)
    - 2001 FS 076 - Collective Action and Technology - Published Material, 2001-2010; 2013:102:002 (Item 2013:102:002)
    - 2001 FS 076 - Fertile Ground? Soil Fertility Management and the African Smallholder - Published Material, 2001-2010; 2013:102:003 (Item 2013:102:003)
    - 2001 FS 087 - TEXAS AGRICULTURAL EXPERIMENT STATION - MAIZE GENETIC IMPROVEMENT AND DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2007 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 097 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - APHID AND VIRUS DISEASE MANAGEMENT IN SEED POTATO PRODUCTION, 2001-2004 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 101 - UNIVERSITY OF QUEENSLAND (AUSTRALIA) - MANUAL ON BREEDING FOR DROUGHT TOLERANCE, 2001-2004 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 101 - Breeding Rice for Drought-Prone Environments - Published and Digital Material, 2001-2004; 2013:102:020, 2013:102:021 (Item 2013:102:020-2013:102:021)
    - 2001 FS 107 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (CIMMYT) - EAST AFRICA REGIONAL MAIZE NURSERY, 1997-2005 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 111 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY MANAGEMENT SERVICES, 2000-2006 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 115 - (FOOD SECURITY) - INFORM POLICY MAKERS REGARDING POOR FARMING HOUSEHOLDS IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2004 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 125 - CARE USA - PRIVATE-SECTOR BASED NETWORK FOR EXPANDED ACCESS TO FARM INPUTS IN ZIMBABWE, 2001-2005 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 129 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - DROUGHT COPING MECHANISMS OF RICE FARMERS, 2001-2004 (Box R4246)
    - 2001 FS 133 - GUEVARA HERNANDEZ, FRANCISCO - SMALLHOLDER FARMING SYSTEMS IN SOUTHERN MEXICO, 2001-2005 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 135 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - TRAINING; EFFECT OF FERTILIZERS ON LOCAL VEGETABLES, 2001-2004 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 136 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - DRYLAND PAPRIKA PRODUCTION AND THE SMALLHOLDER FARMING SECTOR; FIELD TRAINING, 2000-2005 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 140 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; MANAGING SOIL ACIDITY FOR SUSTAINABLE CROP PRODUCTION, 2001-2005 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 145 - (FOOD SECURITY) - INTEGRATED NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT AND SOIL FERTILITY IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2003 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 146 - AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF CHIAPAS (MEXICO) - COLLABORATION FOR AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY INNOVATION, 2001-2005 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 147 - GREEN MANURE COVER CROPS FOUNDATION (MEXICO) - AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY INNOVATION IN CHIAPAS, 2001-2005 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 153 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - CORE SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON SOIL BIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY, 2000-2005 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 157 - JOMO KENYATTA UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE AND TECHNOLOGY (KENYA) - TISSUE CULTURE PROPAGATION OF BANANAS IN CENTRAL KENYA, 2001-2006 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 160 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - MARKER ASSISTED SELECTION IN BREEDING FOR STRESS TOLERANCE IN RICE, 2001-2006 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 161 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - AGRICULTURAL EXTENSION FOR THE UPLANDS OF VIETNAM AND LAOS, 2001-2006 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 161 - Development of Sustainable Land Use Practices in the Uplands for Food Security - Published Material, 2001-2006; 2013:102:004 (Item 2013:102:004)
    - 2001 FS 161 - LUSLOF Booklet Final Report - Digital, 2001-2006; 2013:102:022 (Item 2013:102:022)
    - 2001 FS 161 - APP to LUSLOF Final Report - Digital, 2001-2006; 2013:102:023 (Item 2013:102:023)
    - 2001 FS 162 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND ADVANCED STUDIES OF THE NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE (MEXICO) - ASSESSMENT OF TRANSGENIC MAIZE, 2001-2006 (Box R4247)
    - 2001 FS 165 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY (MOZAMBIQUE) - TRAINING IN AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT, 2001-2006 (Box R4248)
    - 2001 FS 170 - YOUTH FOR ACTION - WOMEN FARMERS IN AGRICULTURAL INNOVATION IN INDIA, 2001-2004 (Box R4248)
    - 2001 FS 171 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - INSTITUTIONAL INNOVATIONS AND SOYBEAN PRODUCTION, 2001-2005 (Box R4248)
    - 2001 FS 183 - BIGIRWA, GEORGE - AFRICAN CAREER AWARD, 2001-2004 (Box R4248)
    - 2001 FS 185 - IMO, MOSES - AFRICAN CAREER AWARD, 2000-2004 (Box R4248)
    - 2001 FS 186 - KITHOME, MUSSOLINI - AFRICAN CAREER AWARD, 2001-2004 (Box R4248)
    - 2002 FS 003 - AKEMO, MARY CHRISTINE - AFRICAN CAREER AWARD, 2001-2005 (Box R4248)
    - 2002 FS 005 - AYAGA, GEORGE ODWAR - AFRICAN CAREER AWARD, 2001-2004 (Box R4248)
    - 2002 FS 006 - ASSOCIATION FOR BETTER LAND HUSBANDRY (KENYA) - SMALLHOLDER FARMERS AND ORGANIC OUTPUT MARKETS, 2001-2006 (Box R4248)
    - 2002 FS 013 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - IMPROVED RICE VARIETIES ADAPTED FOR NORTHERN THAILAND (1 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 2001-2006 (Box R4248)
    - 2002 FS 019 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - IMPROVED COMMUNICATION AND INFORMATION ACCESS, 2001-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 020 - (FOOD SECURITY) - SCIENTIFIC ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 2002-2004 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 023 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; ACCESS TO RURAL FINANCING MARKETS, 2001-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 024 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; CASSAVA MOSAIC VIRUS DISEASE RESISTANCE, 2000-2004 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 025 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; UTILIZATION OF SOYBEANS FOR LIVESTOCK FEED, 2001-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 026 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; CATTLE MANURE AND CROP/LIVESTOCK PRODUCTION SYSTEMS, 2001-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 028 - KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - TECHNOLOGY AND DROUGHT-RELATED COPING STRATEGIES OF FARMERS, 2001-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 036 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - STRIGA RESISTANCE GENES FROM TRIPSACUM AND MAIZE GERMPLASM, 2002-2006 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 046 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; SWEET POTATO PESTS AND DISEASES, 2001-2003 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 047 - CITIZENS NETWORK FOR FOREIGN AFFAIRS - RURAL AGRIBUSINESS SECTOR EXPANSION PROGRAM IN ZIMBABWE, 2001-2004 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 049 - (FOOD SECURITY) - CONFERENCE, "BIOTECHNOLOGY, BREEDING AND SEED SYSTEMS FOR AFRICA", 2002-2006 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 053 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - BIOMETRICS TRAINING AND SERVICES, 1998-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 058 - INTERNATIONAL POTATO CENTER (PERU) - SELECTABLE MARKER FOR USE IN CROP IMPROVEMENT, 2001-2005 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 059 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - FELLOWSHIPS IN MOLECULAR MARKER ASSISTED RICE BREEDING, 2002-2008 (Box R4249)
    - 2002 FS 060 - (FOOD SECURITY) - AFRICAN AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY FOUNDATION, 2002-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 062 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - CONTROL OF STRIGA THROUGH MULTI-PURPOSE TREES AND SHRUBS, 2002-2006 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 064 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - FIELD TRAINING; SMALLHOLDER FARMERS' ACCESS TO AGRICULTURAL KNOWLEDGE AND INFORMATION, 2001-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 068 - (FOOD SECURITY) - PRODUCE MORE RESILIENT CROPS IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2003-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 070 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - RESEARCH TO ENHANCE YAM PRODUCTIONS; FIELD TRAININGS, 2000-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 071 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - SEED BASED TECHNOLOGY AND MOLECULAR MARKER ASSISTED SELECTION IN MAIZE, 2002-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 072 - (FOOD SECURITY) - SEED PRODUCTION AND DISTRIBUTION SYSTEMS IN AFRICA, 2001-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 073 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI - TRAINING IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES; SWEET POTATO WEEVIL MANAGEMENT, 2001-2005 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 074 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; SOIL FERTILITY MANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGIES IN WESTERN KENYA, 2001-2004 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 075 - ALBERT LUDWIGS UNIVERSITY FREIBURG (GERMANY) - PROVITAMIN A-BIOSYNTHESIS IN RICE ENDOSPERM, 1999-2011 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 077 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - SCREENING FOR DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN LANDRACES; IMPROVED GENOTYPES OF RICE FROM INDIA AND IRRI, 2002-2009 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 079 - DONALD DANFORTH PLANT SCIENCE CENTER - BC CONFERENCE: DEVELOPMENT OF A GLOBAL PLAN FOR CASSAVA IMPROVEMENT, 1999-2005 (Box R4254)
    - 2002 FS 085 - (FOOD SECURITY) - BC TEAM: BIOTECHNOLOGY, BREEDING AND SEED SYSTEMS FOR AFRICAN CROPS, 2001-2003 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 088 - UNIVERSITY OF OTTAWA (CANADA) - INSECT RESISTANCE IN AFRICAN CROPS, 2002-2006 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 089 - (FOOD SECURITY) - KENYAN AGRICULTURE STUDY, 2002-2004 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 090 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS, AGRICULTURE AND RURAL RESETTLEMENT (MINISTRY OF) - COWPEA TESTING, SELECTION AND SEED MULTIPLICATION, 2002-2005 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 091 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - MARKER-ASSISTED BREEDING FOR DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN RICE, 2002-2006 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 095 - (FOOD SECURITY) - DEVELOPMENT OF GREATER MEKONG SUB-REGION OF SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2002-2003 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 096 - (FOOD SECURITY) - UGANDAN AGRICULTURE STUDY, 2002-2005 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 099 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - INCORPORATE TRAITS OF "QUALITY PROTEIN MAIZE" TO ENHANCE NUTRITION, 2002-2006 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 101 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP ON INCREASING MACUNA'S POTENTIAL AS A FOOD AND FEED CROP, 2002-2004 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 102 - (FOOD SECURITY) - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 103 - WAGENINGEN UNIVERSITY (NETHERLANDS) - TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN AGRICULTURAL INNOVATION, 2002-2010 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 105 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; TAXONOMY, DISTRIBUTION AND USES OF SANSEVIERIA, 2001-2006 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 107 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - SOIL NUTRIENT DEPLETION IN WEST AFRICA, 2001-2004 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 115 - AFRICA 2000 NETWORK - UGANDA - PILOTING FARMER FIELD SCHOOLS IN UGANDA, 2001-2005 (Box R4255)
    - 2002 FS 116 - NETWORK FOR STUDIES ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MEXICO) - STRENGTHEN COMMUNITY ORGANIZATION AND LOCAL CAPACITY IN OAXACA, MEXICO FOR FARMERS, 2001-2005 (Box R4256)
    - Cuadernillos de Orientacion para el uso de la Agricultura de Cobertura en Mexico (1-4) - Published Material, 2001-2005; 2013:102:010-2013:102:013 (Item 2013:102:010, 2013:102:011, 2013:102:012, 2013:102:013)
    - 2002 FS 117 - (FOOD SECURITY) - MOZAMBICAN AGRICULTURE STUDY, 2002-2004 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 118 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; IMPROVED WEED MANAGEMENT IN SMALLHOLDER INTERCROPPING SYSTEM, 2001-2005 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 118 - Rocks for Crops: Agrominerals of Sub-Saharan Africa - Published Material, 2001-2005; 2013:102:028 (Item 2013:102:028)
    - 2002 FS 119 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; IMPROVING THE PRODUCTIVITY OF LEAFY VEGETABLES, 2002-2004 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 120 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; SOIL FERTILITY AND CROP PRODUCTION (RESCINDED) (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 121 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; SOYBEAN VARIETIES AND INTERCROPPING SYSTEMS, 2002-2005 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 122 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - EAST AFRICAN NARS PARTICIPATION IN DEVELOPING STRESS-TOLERANT MAIZE, 2002-2006 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 125 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - CHINYIKA CROP MANAGEMENT RESEARCH OUTREACH, 2002-2004 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 130 - FUND FOR THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF AGRICULTURAL ECONOMISTS - 25TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE; FACILITATE LINKAGE TO AGRICULTURAL COMMUNITY, 2002-2005 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 133 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MANURE WITH INORGANIC FERTILIZERS AND MAIZE PRODUCTION, 1997-2005 (Box R4256)
    - 2002 FS 135 - SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE CENTRE FOR RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA - ORGANIC RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 2002-2004 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 135 - Format Television Clips Organic Resource Management in Kenya - Audiovidual Material, 2002-2004; 2013:102:014 (Item 2013:102:014)
    - 2002 FS 137 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL COMMODITY EXCHANGE - MARKET INFORMATION AND COMMODITY EXCHANGE SYSTEMS, 2002-2004 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 138 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - NEW RICE FOR AFRICA INITIATIVE, 2002-2006 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 139 - ENVIRONMENTAL ACTION TEAM (KENYA) - BIOLOGICAL ALTERNATIVES FOR SOIL FERTILITY AND MAIZE PRODUCTION, 1995-2005 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 141 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD TRAINING; IMPROVE BEAN SEED QUALITY FOR SMALLHOLDER'S FARMS, 2002-2005 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 143 - CHIANG MAI UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - PARTICIPATORY PLANT BREEDING; DEGREE PROGRAM, 2002-2008 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 143 - Collective Action and Technology Development - Published Material, 2002-2008; 2013:102:016 (Item 2013:102:016)
    - 2002 FS 144 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - MODERNIZE LIBRARY; TRAINING IN BIO-ECONOMICS; SOCIAL-HISTORICAL ANALYSIS OF POVERTY IN KENYA, 2001-2004 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 150 - INTERNATIONAL CROPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR THE SEMI-ARID TROPICS (INDIA) - LEGUME PRODUCTION AND MARKETING IN MALAWI AND MOZAMBIQUE, 2002-2006 (Box R4257)
    - 2002 FS 153 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - IMPROVE PRODUCTION, PROCESSING, AND MARKETING OF CASSAVA, 2002-2005 (Box R4257)